The final test of courage is coming home.
Home of the Brave is a war, drama film directed by Irwin Winkler.
The day after they get the word they'll go home in two weeks, a group
of soldiers from Spokane are ambushed in an Iraqi city.
Back stateside we follow four of them - a surgeon who saw too much, a teacher who's a single mom and who lost a hand in the ambush, an
infantry man whose best friend died that day, and a soldier who keeps reliving the moment he killed a civilian woman.
William Marsh, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Vanessa Price, played by Jessica Biel.
Sarah Schivino, played by Christina Ricci.
Penelope Marsh, played by Victoria Rowell.
Jamal Aiken, played by 50 Cent.
Billy Marsh, played by Sam Jones.
Home of the Brave is a 2006 American drama film written and
directed by Irwin Winkler starring Samuel L.
Jackson, Jessica Biel, Brian Presley, Curtis Jackson, Christina Ricci and Chad Michael Murray that follows
the lives of four Army National Guard soldiers in Iraq and their return to the United States.
The film was shot in Ouarzazate, Morocco and in Spokane, Washington.
The film was released by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer on December 20, 2006.
It was a critical and box office bomb.
The film explores themes of post-traumatic stress disorder
(ptsd), iraq war veteran, u.s. soldier.
The tone is emotional.